const fips200CardData = [
    {
        "Front": "What is an information system?",
        "Back": "A discrete set of information resources for the collection, processing, maintenance, use, sharing, dissemination, or disposition of information."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What are information resources?",
        "Back": "Information resources include information and resources such as personnel, equipment, funds, and information technology."
    },
    {
        "Front": "How many minimum security requirement areas are there?",
        "Back": "17"
    },
    {
        "Front": "What are the 17 areas of minimum security requirements defined by FIPS-200?",
        "Back": "Access Control; Awareness and Training; Audit and Accountability; Certfication, Accreditation and Security Assessments; Configuration Management; Contingency Planning; Identification and Authentication; Incident Response; Maintenance; Media Protection; Physical and Environmental Protection; Planning; Personnel Security; Risk Assessment; Systems and Services Acquisition; System and Communication Protection; System and Information Integrity"
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Access Control (AC)?",
        "Back": "Limit system use to authorized users performing authorized functions."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Awareness and Training (AT)?",
        "Back": "Ensuring that personnel are aware of the security risks associated with their use of an information system and that they are properly trained to carry out their assigned information security duties."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Audit and Accountability (AU)?",
        "Back": "Production and retention of information system audit records for analysis of unauthorized system activity and ensuring that actions of users can be uniquely traced for accountability."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Certification, Accreditation, and Security Assessments (CA)?",
        "Back": "The periodic assessment of security controls used to develop and implement plans of action to correct deficiencies. The authorization of information systems and connections and the monitoring of security controls on an ongoing basis."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Configuration Mangement (CM)?",
        "Back": "The establishment and maintenance of baseline configurations and inventories of information systems throughout the SDLC. The establishment and enforcement of security configuration settings."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Contingency Planning (CP)?",
        "Back": "The establishment, maintenance, and effective implementation of plans for emergency response, backup operations and post-disaster recovery."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Identification and Authentication (IA)?",
        "Back": "Organizations must identify and authenticate information system users."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Incident Response (IR)?",
        "Back": "The establishment of incident handling capabilites for an information system including adequate prep, detection, analysis, containment and recovery and the proper reporting of those incidents."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Maintenance (MA)?",
        "Back": "Performance of periodic maintenance of information systems with effective controls on the tools used to conduct that maintenance."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Media Protection (MP)?",
        "Back": "The protection of both paper and digital system media by limiting access to authorized users and the proper destruction of before disposal."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Physical and Environment (PE)?",
        "Back": "Organizations must limit physical access to authorized individuals, protect the physical plant and support infrastructure, provide supporting utilities, and protect against environmental hazards using appropriate environmental controls.."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Planning (PL)?",
        "Back": "Development, documentation and maintenance of security plans that describe security controls in place and the rules of behavior for accessing the information system."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is Risk Assessment (RA)?",
        "Back": "Periodic assessment of the risk to operations, assets, and individuals."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is System and Services Acquisition (SA)?",
        "Back": "Allocation of sufficient resources to adequately protect information systems. Use SDLC processes that incorporate information security considerations. Develop and employ software usage and installation restrictions and ensure third party providers use adequate security measures."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is System and Communication Protection (SC)?",
        "Back": "Monitor, control, and protect communications at both internal and external boundaries and promote and use security focused processes."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is System and Information Integrity (SI)?",
        "Back": "Idenitification and correction of information system flaws in a timely manner. Providing protections from malicious code, and monitoring information security alerts and taking action when appropriate."
    },

]

export default fips200CardData;